<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Intern</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/amberscript-software-dev-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/amberscript-software-dev-intern/</guid>
      <description>Interning With a Successful SaaS Start Up At Amberscript, I took ownership over many projects to make everyday business operations more efficient.&#xA;Using automations tools such as UI Bakery, JavaScript and Google Apps Script I have successfully crafted systems to ensure speedy freelancer management and payout processes for the finance and operations team.&#xA;Using webhooks, UI Bakery Automations and Slack + other various APIs, I have created a helper Slack bot, which allowed the use of commands to quickly acomplish everyday actions for all employees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Programming and Sound Design Intern</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/auris-media-audio-programming-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/auris-media-audio-programming-intern/</guid>
      <description>Programming Audio Into Games During my internship year at Coventry University I have worked with an audio post-production boutique, Auris Media.&#xA;During my time with them I have created high-quality sound assets using Nuendo and integrated into Unreal Engine 5 through Wwise middleware, enhancing the immersive qualities of interactive media projects.&#xA;Showcased my strong skills in audio programming by developing, optimizing, and debugging efficient audio systems.&#xA;Collaborated with multidisciplinary teams, providing creative solutions for audio-related project needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/codiblox-owner-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/codiblox-owner-copy/</guid>
      <description>Launching My Own Programming School After being laid off, I have bootstrapped and managed an online tutoring business, teaching Python to young children online.&#xA;To effectively lead online lessons I have developed a robust videoconferencing architecture to deliver online lessons, I explored and evaluated platforms such as Jitsi, Google Meet, Zoom, Microsoft Teams and BigBlueButton.&#xA;In pursuit of expanding my clientele I have conducted thorough market research and implemented A/B testing to my ads and website, maximizing user engagement and CPA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Instructor</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/codetoday-coding-instructor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/codetoday-coding-instructor/</guid>
      <description>Teaching Others the Joy of Programming During my time at Coventry University, I was also working as a Coding Instructor for a London-based tutoring company, Codetoday.&#xA;During my lessons I have effectively led students in coding, and exhibited exceptional communication skills, conveying complex programming concepts in a simple and engaging manner.&#xA;To make programming accessible and enjoyable for students of all ages, I adapted my teaching style. Maintained an approachable and friendly demeanor while also commanding respect when necessary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SketchUp Ray Tracing Plugin</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/sketchup-first-reflections-plugin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/sketchup-first-reflections-plugin/</guid>
      <description>Technologies: Ruby, RubyMine IDE, SketchUp SDK, GitHub&#xA;SketchUp Ray Tracing Plugin that simulates ray reflections in a 3D environment. The plugin allows users to visualize sound reflections by casting rays from a selected surface within SketchUp models. It is designed to assist in architectural acoustic design by providing a quick and easy way to simulate sound-wave behavior in various environments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Plug-In Suite</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/audio-plugin-suite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/audio-plugin-suite/</guid>
      <description>This is a set of 3 plug-ins, which can be used in Digital Audio Workstations to process audio. Built with JUCE, C++ and Max MSP.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity Samurai Village Game</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/samurai-village-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 09:53:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/samurai-village-game/</guid>
      <description>Technologies: C#, Unity, GitLab, FMOD, Reaper&#xA;This project is an immersive 3rd-person adventure game focused on showcasing my game audio implementation and C# programming skills. It features a menu system, dynamic water audio system (with depth detection), foliage audio, footsteps audio, dialogue, music implementation, quest music variation.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
